JONATHAN COMBERBACH

Full stack developer passionate about designing web applications that effortlessly blend functionality, design, and user experience. I want to provide the user with a sense of adventure when they explore all an app has to offer. 5 years of hospitality makes me a big fan of slinging drinks and telling stories.

IONATHAN.COMBERBACH@GMAIL.COM

604-346-6925

LinkedIn: jonathan-comberbach

GitHub: @comberj

SKILLS

Top Languages: Javascript, TypeScript, Coldfusion.

Other Language Proficiencies: Python, SQL, Ruby.

Libraries & Frameworks: React, Angular, VueJs, nodeJS, Express, Fusebox, Jasmine.

Tools: Git, Atom, VsCode, Sublime, Azure Data Studio.

Other: Component design, UX.

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Labs | September 2018

Intensive web development bootcamp focused on emulating the web developer workflow using modern languages and frameworks through a project-based curriculum.

University of British Columbia
August 2010 - May 2014
B.A in Psychology

EMPLOYMENT

FABRIC

Software Engineer | August 2020 - Present

- Planned and developed the decoupling of several microservices
- Worked primarily on back-end task and architecture tasks.
 Investigated several routes we could pursue to increase our scaling capabilities and reduce the amount of code present in our codebase.
- Weighed and assessed several different potential partnerships in regards to tax, payment, and other necessary e-commerce services.

WINEDIRECT

Jr. Software Developer | Jan 2019 - August 2020

- Planned, scoped and developed the company's two most highly requested features, satisfying 1200 clients.
- Designed and implemented a working graphQL solution in Fusebox to upgrade from REST APIs.
- Improved performance in the most frequently used client workflow by over 60% (3s to 1s).
- Refreshed an outdated look and feel, completely rebuilding part of a 19-year-old application from the ground up in a modern framework.

BETTERHOURS

Co-Founder | Oct 2019 - Present

- Co-founded a company to help coffee shops and shift-based businesses better organize their staff and save dozens of hours on their scheduling. At its core, it's a smart scheduler, which uses linear programming to find a globally optimal employee shift schedule by taking advantage of convex optimization.
- Worked primarily on the front-end of the application to refresh and rebuild a jQuery-based web-app in VueJs.
- Wrote the first version of a react-native based mobile version for the employee side of the application.

Ніднціднтѕ

VANCOUVER STARTUP WEEK

September 2019

- One of four panelists talking about accessibility on the web.
- Discussed my work bringing WineDirect's client templates up to 100% ADA compliance.

INTERNSHIP PROGRAM

January 2020 - Present

- In charge of selecting candidates, interviewing, and ultimately hiring an intern at WineDirect.
- Acted as supervisor and mentor throughout the internship.